// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
      question: "Who developed the Python language?",
    answer: "Guido van Rossum",
    options: [
      "Zim Den",
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Niene Stom",
      "Wick van Rossum"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which one of the following is the correct extension of the Python file?",
    answer: ".py",
    options: [
      ".py",
      ".python",
      ".p",
      ".None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What do we use to define a block of code in Python language?",
    answer: "Indentation",
    options: [
      "Key",
      "Brackets",
      "Indentation",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following declarations is incorrect?",
    answer: "None of these",
    options: [
      "_x = 2",
      "__x = 3",
      "__xyz__ = 5",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a keyword in Python language?",
    answer: "val",
    options: [
      "val",
      "raise",
      "try",
      "with"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following words cannot be a variable in python language?",
    answer: "try",
    options: [
      "_val",
      "val",
      "try",
      "_try_"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following functions is a built-in function in python language?",
    answer: "print()",
    options: [
      "val()",
      "print()",
      "fetch()",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Given a function that does not return any value, What value is thrown by default when executed in shell.",
    answer: "None",
    options: [
      "int",
      "bool",
      "void",
      "None"
    ]
  },
     {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the return type of function id?",
    answer: "int",
    options: [
      "int",
      "float",
      "bool",
      "dict"
    ]
  },   {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Syntax error in python is detected by _________at _______",
    answer: "interpreter/ run time",
    options: [
      "compiler/ compile time",
      "interpreter/ run time",
      "Compiler/ run time",
      "interpreter/ compile time"
    ]
  },

];